hi spring bend and today's installment
嗨， Spring 弯和今天的分期付款
of spring tips I'm going to take a look
Spring 的技巧，我要看看
at some alternatives to low-level sequel
在一些低水平续集的替代方案中
when you're doing data access with a
当您使用
sequel based database or our DBMS we'll
基于续集的数据库或我们的DBMS
start today with my babies now for those
从今天开始，我的孩子们
of you have been in the Java industry
你们中的一些人从事过Java行业
for more than 10 years you'll know that
十多年来，你会知道
my business was at one point a project
我的业务是某个项目
called ideas and I business started by
叫做想法，我的业务始于
Clinton begin gosh it's got to be at
克林顿开始大放异彩
least 10 15 years now in 2001 - I'm not
现在至少有15年15年-2001年
even sure but it came up in the early
即使可以肯定，但它在早期就出现了
days around the same time as hibernate
冬眠的同一天
in spring so I remember it fondly at the
在 Spring ，所以我深深地记得
time there was very few sort of good
时间很少有什么好
open options for persistence for people
为人们提供持久性的开放选择
mapping right for object relational
对象关系的映射权
mapping I remember at the time there's
我记得当时的地图
also Apache ojd for example right so
也像Apache ojd这样吧
there's a lot of you know there's been a
你们很多人都知道
lot of options that have come and gone
来来去去的很多选择
but I data sits now in a you know now
但是我的数据现在坐在一个你现在知道的地方
named my business at Apache has gone the
命名我在Apache的业务
distance it survived as long as spring
它生存到 Spring 的距离
as and more you know and so that makes
随着越来越多的你知道，所以这使得
it a certainly a choice worth looking
这无疑是一个值得一看的选择
into one thing that's been very
变成一件事，已经非常
interesting to me in my in my travels
在旅行中对我来说很有趣
when I thought to bring community
当我想带社区
members and users all around the world
世界各地的会员和用户
is it while I don't hear much about -
是不是在我不怎么了解的情况下-
here in the West it is extraordinarily
在西方，这里非常
popular in China very very popular so in
在中国很受欢迎
fact some of the largest websites on the
事实上，
planet are using my data at scale so
地球正在大规模使用我的数据，因此
that that's that's a volumes righted -
那就是正确的数量-
it still got a very large active user
它仍然有很大的活跃用户
base there it's still being you know
根据那里仍然是你知道
evolved it's still very much in demand
演变它仍然非常需求
so it makes it it makes me think we
所以它让我觉得我们
should revisit it and so I think it's a
应该重新审视它，所以我认为这是一个
good choice or today's spring tip so
不错的选择或今天的 Spring 提示
we're going to do is going to build a
我们要做的是建立一个
spring application here which can call
Spring 的应用程序可以在这里调用
this my latest demo I will use the auto
这是我最新的演示，我将使用自动
configuration for my business now this
现在我的业务配置
integration is not developed by the
集成不是由
spring booting proper it's actually has
spring boot 适当，实际上有
been built by the my beta team and I'm
由我的Beta团队建立，我是
happy to to share that I also contribute
分享我也很乐意分享
to this auto configuration this support
对这种自动配置的支持
on my latest project after seeing the
在看到我的最新项目后
demand for it on demand for my biggest
对我最大的需求
integration with spring boot there are
与spring boot集成还有
other people that actually act
实际行动的其他人
contribute to this and it's maintained
对此做出贡献并得到维护
by the native team so it's really you
由本地团队来完成，所以实际上是您
know it's always evolving it's always
知道它总是在不断发展
going and that team make sure that it's
去，那个团队确保它是
pretty good auto-configuration is the
很好的自动配置是
best and breed sort of support possible
最好的和可能的支持
so I'm gonna use my business to news h22
所以我要用我的生意来新闻
an in-memory embedded sequel database
内存中嵌入式续集数据库
because it'll make it much easier for us
因为这会使我们更容易
to prototype something I'm going to use
为我要使用的东西制作原型
long box because I want to I want to
长盒子，因为我想要我想要
spend too much time building up the
花太多时间建立
object we're going to persist into the
对象，我们将坚持到
air like this door so I'll build a a dko
空气像这扇门，所以我要建一个dko
of cold gel write something something
冷凝胶写点东西
that will get mapped to our underlying
将被映射到我们的基础
data store and then that should do so go
数据存储，然后应该这样做
ahead we'll go ahead and get generate
前进，我们将继续前进并产生
and open this up in our IDE
并在我们的IDE中打开它
you
您
okay so what we have here is a new
好，所以我们这里有一个新的
applications single application we're
应用程序我们是单个应用程序
going to you know as you as I typically
像我平常一样去找你
do I'm going to contrive a simple
我会做一个简单的
example so that's language which
例子，那是语言
supports okay tan in signified car and
支持标志性汽车中的棕褐色，并且
that will give us a few years give me a
那会给我们几年的时间给我一个
Lombok dated class so a lot of bucks a
龙目岛约会班所以很多钱
little bit of background today of Java
Java的今天背景
preprocessor sort of sleep is so Java
预处理器的睡眠是如此Java
agent settle before turn the compilation
代理在转编之前就解决
it'll add things based on these compile
它会基于这些编译添加东西
time and cases in this case is if I
在这种情况下的时间和情况是
create phenyl here called a nice model
在这里创建苯基称为好模型
won't get automatic feeders and centers
不会获得自动进纸器和中心
for those fields of added setter and a
对于添加的二传手和
few other four-year and of course we
其他的四年，当然我们
need a co-chair for this to the IEP
需要为此担任IEP的联合主席
right so when assistance all that if I
是的，所以当我帮忙的时候
want to you know work with this I would
想要您知道与此一起工作吗
need to create a an interest in and set
需要引起兴趣并设置
the field so if I call on the setter so
现场，所以如果我打电话给二传手
I'll have a long box generate an all
我将有一个长箱子产生所有
argument constructor and they no argues
论证的建设者，他们没有争论
construction so I can easily create them
施工，所以我可以轻松地创建它们
in up yes econ said let me just see
是的，econ说让我看看
constructor based construction and now
基于构造函数的构造和现在
what I need to do a new build of save
我需要做的新的保存
and work with instances of the theta so
并使用theta实例
you know also about my manliness which
你也知道我的男子气概
is what spring this coming up in a bit
是 Spring 来了
that's when seeing or activated on
在看到或激活时
startup and I will launch through insert
启动，我将通过插入启动
some data in the database here and I
我这里和我数据库中的一些数据
want to do that using my bin it's not a
想要使用我的垃圾箱来做到这一点，这不是
central concept with my beta is this
我的Beta的中心概念是
idea of a sequel matter of a it's a
一个续集的想法是
thing that sells my bait is how to take
卖我的鱼饵的方法是如何服用
method invocations and turn them into
方法调用并将其转换为
executions over the other giving sequel
处决其他续集
query fine so my biggest the sequels
查询很好，所以我最大的续集
that you're using is very much funny
你使用的很有趣
center so this is a nice choice if you
中心，所以这是一个不错的选择
want full control of the underlying
想要完全控制底层
sequels the underlying sort of specifics
安排基本细节
of query diesel and all the queries that
查询柴油和所有的查询
are being using them online Vedas just
正在网上使用吠陀经
beautiful and I think this is good ideas
美丽，我认为这是个好主意
for building an application using editor
使用编辑器构建应用程序
semester you want to do is try and treat
你想做的一个学期就是尝试和治疗
it like a dumb code budget where you
就像是愚蠢的代码预算
create read update delete introduced by
创建读取更新删除者
their ID and and ignore the real power
他们的ID而忽略了真正的力量
that I'll definitely solar should be
我肯定会太阳能
analytic skateboard so
解析滑板所以
there's a couple of different ways you
您有几种不同的方式
can give my data sets at mapper but
可以在mapper上给我数据集，但是
first and I think the most inspire so
首先，我认为最启发的是
approachable is just to create a
平易近人只是为了创造一个
declarative interface here so I'm going
声明式接口，所以我要去
to create a car mapper and I'll annotate
创建一个汽车映射器，我会注释
it with the idea of my videos on Mac or
它与我在Mac上的视频或
annotation here and I'm going to create
在这里注释，我将创建
a few methods here so I guess we need a
这里有一些方法，所以我想我们需要一个
unit select we need a select method we
单元选择我们需要选择方法
made a method defines all the records by
提出了一种方法来定义所有记录
ID so let's say expression or less all
ID，所以我们说表达式或全部
and you can annotate those you can
你可以注释那些
answer this project with an annotation
用注解回答这个项目
to signal through my data what is query
通过我的数据表示什么是查询
that no one uses force less awesome car
没有人使用力更强的汽车
and that will look like the results from
这看起来像是来自
this query only when we create it we're
这个查询只有当我们创建它时
going to make sure that the result from
将确保结果来自
the query give us a sign called make
查询给我们一个叫做make的标志
model and an ID and my business will
型号和ID，以及我的业务
convert that result set back into a
将该结果集转换回
photo for us it will explore the type of
为我们拍照，它将探索
photos from this return value here and
来自此返回值的照片在这里和
bundle up in field selection
捆绑现场选择
and that's it alright so I guess we need
没关系，所以我想我们需要
a we need a stable first we'll go here
我们需要一个稳定的人，我们先去这里
and cut a new schema we call again
并剪切一个新架构，我们再次调用
assume that sequel is a spring framework
假设续集是Spring Framework
JDBC mechanism finds it'll it'll be
JDBC机制找到了
evaluated when the application starts up
在应用程序启动时进行评估
you can also sort of data that you can
您还可以对数据进行排序
also for the data of people you can also
也可以用于人的数据
sort of data that sequel that will get
那种会得到续集的数据
evaluated at this community for this and
为此在该社区进行了评估，并
evaluate if you subscribe your team
评估您是否订阅团队
layer DDL here all here we're going to
DDL层，这就是我们要做的全部
say that we will use each to also stop
说我们将使用每个也停止
tables is this cause then we'll say a
表是这个原因，那么我们将说
quick table cause and we're going to
快速表原因，我们将要
have a couple seals you said going to
你说过要去印章
have an ID or serial not null is a big
有一个ID或序列号不为null很大
big integer then we're going to take a
大整数，那么我们将采用
fielder for the make for the safar cause
为探险事业而努力
not know as well and then on to the
还不知道，然后继续
model that I bought all this thing so
我买了所有东西的模特
that mole and another one for the year
那只痣和一年中的另一只
or for not null and format data format
或用于非null和格式数据格式
like that okay legal so very fine and I
像这样的合法法律，很好，我
still experience so yeah so a little bit
仍然经历如此，是的，那么一点点
a year a little bit that'll be able to
一年一点就能
think of this is a primary key we're
认为这是我们的主键
gonna have to worry about that too much
不得不担心太多
well we'll see that we'll see how we
好吧，我们将看到，我们将看到我们如何
have to care about that only insert
只在乎那只插入
records so there's that but it'll be a
记录，所以有，但这将是一个
select we need to be able to insert
选择我们需要能够插入
records right let's the fourth the next
记录正确，让我们接下来的第四个
thing this is an important so looks for
事情很重要，所以寻找
now he will try to go this is for the
现在他将尝试去这是为了
destination by a place because the
一个地方的目的地，因为
finish line here when I say sweat balls
当我说出汗球时在这里完成
and visit every single message that
并访问每条消息
comes back and experiment works for
回来进行实验
Faulkner order that's all we need to
福克纳订单就是我们所需要的
have to datum a database in the first
必须先在数据库中建立基准
place which gives us two leading a
这个地方让我们两个领先
inserts that's so good and insert here
插入效果很好，然后插入此处
will say research into cars on make
会说对汽车制造的研究
model years
模特年
values make model year so what we're
价值观决定了模特年，所以我们
doing here is we're writing a sequel
这样做是我们在写续集
statement and you're using a special
声明，而您正在使用特殊
syntax agent image that we're using a
我们正在使用的语法代理图片
special syntax in the sequel statement
续集语句中的特殊语法
this is the expression expression that I
这是我的表达表达
think going through OD NL which is
认为要通过OD NL
object at Knossos at least in its
至少在克诺索斯
navigation notation language that is
导航符号语言是
also for the old technologies is some of
对于旧技术来说，
you may remember it's excusing things
您可能还记得这很有趣
like web work and tapestry examples
像网络工作和挂毯的例子
within our drivers is a very venerable
在我们的司机中是非常可敬的
put in a query or expression language
使用查询或表达语言
but the point is if we're evaluating
但是关键是如果我们正在评估
here a field that's set against the
这里是一个反对
context so this will correspond to the
上下文，因此这将对应于
car and the car that model card up makes
汽车和模型卡组成的汽车
card up here that we pass into the
卡在这里，我们进入
sender to be a partner of the insert
发件人为插入的合作伙伴
method nib so that's does that now if we
方法笔尖，如果我们现在就这样做
want to be able to make sure that when
希望能够确保何时
this car is asserted that this returned
这辆车被断言这辆车还回来了
ID is object has if you leaf established
如果您建立了叶子，则ID是对象拥有的ID
auto incrementing
自动递增
our key set on the object itself that is
我们在对象本身上设置的密钥是
imperative so these just deserves all
势在必行，所以这些都值得
this IP is so we need to specify an
该IP，因此我们需要指定一个
option with options and you can see that
选项和选项，您可以看到
it was you knew sooner in key equals
那是你早知道关键对等
false by default in the fake food and
默认情况下，在假冒食物中为假，并且
that should give us you know another
那应该给我们你知道另一个
message key things in access let me say
消息访问中的关键事项让我说
leave that as it is car under a little
离开它，因为它是车下一点
it feels heavy but we've got a Honda
感觉很沉重，但是我们有本田
Civic
思域
thank you for know alrighty and another
谢谢你知道好，另一个
one of these once am BMW 330i 2012 and
其中之一是BMW 330i 2012，
also have a finicky 260 only 1500 that
也有挑剔的260只有1500
there's a few cars here
这里有几辆车
and so I'm going to variable and I'm
所以我要去变数
going to be fit every single records in
将适合每个记录
that event is here and we're going to
该事件在这里，我们将要
display and put it using our quadratic
显示并使用我们的二次方
for car mats insert and if anything goes
用于汽车垫插入，如果有的话
to plan I should both then drag
计划我都应该然后拖
everything over to fly out of there goes
一切飞出那里去
we print them out here or should see
我们在这里打印出来或应该看到
that these objects not have ID I'll find
这些对象没有ID我会找到
them even though they will know Susan
他们即使知道苏珊
and so actually can fit a sub service
所以实际上可以适合子服务
you can say for each car here on NASA
您可以在NASA上为每辆车说
research car and then call what you
研究车，然后叫你
think so now about to see before we do
现在想想，然后再做
this let's although to see this place
尽管让我们看到这个地方
there's three records on the consult
咨询中有三个记录
with your IDs then we'll see all three
与您的ID，然后我们将看到所有三个
at the same time and justice partition
同时与司法分区
things off all makes a little bit
一切都变得有点
explicit that means that that is one
明确的意味着那是一个
thing happening out together so I think
事情一起发生，所以我认为
that's enough to get started let's go
足以开始，让我们开始吧
ahead give that a whirl
向前旋转
all right delivers a live our three
好吧，我们的三个人
records are inserted here there's the
记录插入在这里
three cars with their Auto implemented
实施了自动驾驶的三辆汽车
Cheryl ID like has been assigned so he
Cheryl ID像已被分配，所以他
is sort of an outsider we said before in
是我们之前所说的局外人
and on the inside of that executions I
在那行刑的内部
have the sounder vailable CIP available
有可用的发声器可用CIP
and here we can confirm that that is
在这里我们可以确认那是
actually assisted forms automatic forth
实际辅助表格自动
about doing a crosswalk you can do you
关于人行横道，你可以做到
know this is what other things we could
知道这是我们还能做的其他事情
city here we for them kind of method
这里的城市，我们为他们提供一种方法
good police please please delete by ID
好警察，请按身份证删除
long algae or you can just long are
长藻或你可以长
these in this case police believe from
这些在这种情况下，警方相信
car where I do these both IV and that
我做这些IV和那个的车
would give us what we expect we can do
会给我们我们期望我们能做的
an insert but what I really like is on
插入，但我真正喜欢的是
to exert a dynamic search method of in
运用动态搜索方法
search for all the cars that have either
搜索所有具有
a maze or a model over here or all three
这里的迷宫或模型或全部三个
of them I don't any combination is also
其中我没有任何组合也是
service I'm going to create a search
服务，我要创建一个搜索
method but it's not what you need to do
方法，但这不是您需要做的
this dynamically what I want to do on
这是我想做的动态
the dynamically create the query if
动态创建查询，如果
these things are not know or if they're
这些东西不知道，或者如果它们是
not zero necessity here but if they're
这里不是零必要，但如果他们是
not there I don't want them to be
不在那里，我不想他们成为
computed this query and of course he's
计算了这个查询，他当然是
clearing are in the annotations
清除在注释中
themselves which means that I can't do
自己，这意味着我做不到
any kind of system conditional logic in
任何类型的系统条件逻辑
the sanitation so another way by image
卫生，所以通过图像的另一种方式
to describe a mapper to my business is
描述我的业务的映射者是
to use an XML file and this is actually
使用XML文件，这实际上是
the mechanism that predates the sort of
这种机制早于
Education Center support to use it
教育中心支持使用它
because my base itself create annotation
因为我的基地本身会创建注释
experiments like spring today ten
像今天 Spring 的十个实验
fifteen twenty so what we're going to do
15点20分，我们要做的是
is going to create a mapper
将要创建一个映射器
XML on the coffee area existing file
咖啡区域现有文件上的XML
here which has the basic skeleton of of
这里具有的基本骨架
our mapper for example here source a
例如我们的映射器在这里来源
source main resources and select here I
源主要资源，然后在此处选择我
need to create a new directory next on
接下来需要创建一个新目录
example and we'll move commerce about
示例，我们将围绕
XML to your sound example open this up
XML到您的声音示例中打开它
and it is better
而且更好
so socks standard a basic empty my my
所以袜子标准的基本空我
baby so female here I need to tell the
宝贝，所以在这里我要告诉女性
main space for this particular matter I
这件事的主要空间我
need to give it things to be a classic
需要把它变成经典
self right so this used to be optional
自我权利，所以这曾经是可选的
Mouse
老鼠
I think all that's required as you
我认为您需要做的所有事情
believe medically required right now so
相信现在需要医疗，所以
it's a good idea and then here we're
这是一个好主意，然后在这里
going to Friday's a select query for the
去星期五的选择查询
search method and the Sussex going will
搜索方法和苏塞克斯会去
see as you expect us all from car but
看到您对汽车的期望，但是
then we want to provide a where clause
那么我们想提供一个where子句
for some things made dynamically
对于一些动态制作的东西
contributors so that they wear if less
贡献者，以使他们少穿
if ID does not equal 0 and ID says not
如果ID不等于0并且ID表示不
equal null IDs people are you so we're
等于空ID的人是您，所以我们
going to contribute the string if the
如果
test is true yes yes make does not equal
测试为是是是使不相等
null and makes this course right now one
null并立即进行本课程
thing you may be wondering is what
你可能想知道的是什么
happens if for example this is a service
例如，如果这是一项服务，则会发生
my business fun enough to go through and
我的生意很有趣，可以经历
remove that extraneous for the successes
删除多余的成功
and industry so those little in the
和工业，所以那些在
Vitamix you select all some Carl's where
Vitamix您选择所有Carl的地方
make equals whatever you put that in
等于你所投入的
forever
永远
so it'll automatically remove the prefix
因此它将自动删除前缀
and forth making it like you either give
来回使它就像你给
the whole thing and still look at the
整个事情，仍然看
clear in your head and then so would
清除你的头脑，然后
happen we're going to create another
碰巧我们要创建另一个
cost here so it's a model it's not equal
成本在这里，所以它是一个模型，它是不相等的
no and say and model should equal muck
不，说和模型应该相等
welcome to maven is it up here I use and
欢迎来到Maven，我在这里用吗？
like this is a useful place for an XML
像这样对于XML来说是一个有用的地方
document just causes a parking error so
文档只会导致停车错误，因此
we're just going to and like this and I
我们只是要去像这样，我
think that will do so if you the CTO is
认为如果您的CTO是
encrypted then this default behaviour if
加密然后默认行为
you feel finest products or a farmer
你觉得最好的产品或农民
with a zero for the ID this is just plus
ID为零，这只是加号
everything from the daily
每天的一切
we can you know qualify our predicator
我们可以知道我们的谓词是否合格
our search by let's find anyone with us
通过我们的搜索让我们找到任何人
we plan is going to end
我们计划要结束
try that in action here so go back to
尝试在这里行动，所以回到
our code block here at a new partition
我们的代码块在新分区
almost like parm a sandbox search and
几乎就像parm一样，沙盒搜索和
we're gonna supply these that you want
我们将提供您想要的这些
the Honda and nothing else when I can
本田，我什么时候都可以
specify the model over here and if
在这里指定模型，如果
everything goes to plan we should get
一切都按计划进行，我们应该得到
one little fact
一个小事实
now this interface I said the promise
现在这个界面我说了诺
yes
是
and these partners are not obvious and
这些伙伴并不明显，
will not visible to the two runtimes
这两个运行时将不可见
reflection right if you have a Java
如果您有Java，则可以进行反射
class in Java 8 or later they differ up
Java 8或更高版本中的类，它们有所不同
to good love the information or rather
善待信息或宁可
the metadata about that school friend
关于那个学校朋友的元数据
this is outpaces the reflection
这超过了反思
hierarchy for concrete classes in
具体类的层次结构
previous versions of Java you could use
您可以使用的Java的早期版本
the bug information to get the
错误信息以获取
information about what the man is
关于这个男人是什么的信息
planning block but even as of Java 8
规划块，甚至从Java 8开始
there is no way through reflection so
没有办法通过反思，所以
applicaiton the name of your planner so
申请计划者的姓名，以便
you need this energy like if you ever
你需要这种能量，就像你曾经
use spring data JP or anything you can
使用spring数据JP或任何您可以使用的数据
get it you know that we had the same
得到它，你知道我们有相同的
thing when you're trying to you trying
当你想尝试的时候
to expose the poly choice for network
揭露网络的多元化选择
logs or so let say that you've helped
日志或大约说您有所帮助
the frame what's the name of the planet
框架这颗行星的名字是什么
folks make it something names make model
乡亲们把它变成了名字使模型成为现实
with the names model
与名称模型
um year living in view so let's see with
嗯，一年的生活，让我们一起来看
that that's one search by the Honda
那是本田的搜寻
and we have something wrong in search on
而且我们在搜索中出了点问题
Norris insulin doses or IDs not Tara
诺里斯（Norris）胰岛素剂量或ID（不是IDA）
that you care about they make the model
您在乎他们制作的模型
and the year that lady is my fault
那年那位女士是我的错
aha so exactly saying that it doesn't
啊哈，正好说不
know how to take the data comes back to
知道如何获取数据
this and give it to a few something that
这并给它一些东西
we can use so we need to say that we
我们可以使用，所以我们需要说
don't I'm keeping calm that examples are
我是否保持冷静，例子是
car which is obvious to my beta simple
这辆车对我的beta版很明显
signature with the annotations but
带有注释的签名，但是
remember we're not we're not trading or
记住我们不是我们不是在交易或
activated this particular matter to an
激活了这件事
incision we're using XML so we need to
切口，我们正在使用XML，因此我们需要
be a little bit more redundant of course
当然多一点多余
exclusive and that done we get a result
排他性的，我们得到了结果
for everything is working as we expected
一切都按我们预期的那样工作
that likes them so I'm switching them up
喜欢他们，所以我要切换他们
with these you know it's if you happen
与这些你知道这是如果你发生
to the first to Flanders it's a summer
到法兰德斯的第一个夏天
on the left end result so those who are
在左端结果，所以那些谁是
women winner is welcome and 100 people
欢迎女性获胜者和100人
sit here ok mole also want the 30 I knew
坐在这里好吧mole鼠也想要30我知道
your 0 if you still see one method this
如果您仍然看到一种方法，则为0
is video 6 over 3 life
是3生命中的影片6
all right that seems to be working fine
一切正常，看起来还不错
good now let's try all feelings and no
现在好，让我们尝试所有的感觉，没有
for everything no no I'm here and so 10
对于所有的一切，不，不，我在这里，所以10
nothing else they should see all three
他们没有其他应该看到的全部三个
records I registered on the console is
我在控制台上注册的记录是
recording I recorded on the console and
我在控制台上录制的录音
then we go on desks and if you say this
那我们去桌子上，如果你这么说
often does that work so we've looked at
通常会做这项工作，所以我们已经研究了
how to build a very simple equals map
如何建立一个非常简单的平等地图
reasons of my babies this is a
我的孩子的原因这是一个
technology that's good because sometimes
技术很好，因为有时
they use with some of the largest
他们使用一些最大的
websites on the planet again see you on
地球上的网站再次在
some huge website Federation leather for
一些巨大的网站联盟皮革
billions of people in China it's a very
中国数十亿人
very powerful tool and I encourage you
非常强大的工具，我鼓励您
to take a look at it and if you want
看看它，如果你想
some it is lightweight and fast and
有些是轻巧，快速的
approachable and findable and still I
平易近人，但我仍然
think very early gift finder it's hard
认为很早就找到礼物的人很难
to argue at the alien sense of this
争论这种异端感
month of mappers a little bit more
映射者的月份多一点
robust a little bit more on hideous
在可怕方面更强大
ladies then you send to service a
女士们，那么你送去服务
convention center spring data repository
会议中心 spring data 存储库
interface but it's run that's the same
界面，但运行相同
thing line such as Pacific here you're
像太平洋这样的东西
forced to provide bigquery which is fine
被迫提供bigquery很好
it's not all that bad and you can do
并没有那么糟糕，你可以做
other kinds of tests before cleansing is
清洁前的其他测试
worth noting that's my bit of support
值得一提的是我的支持
providing the same query in the XML
在XML中提供相同的查询
using conditions you can say okay if the
使用条件，如果
data is right now is HQ provide this
数据现在是总部提供的
query bit Explorer hostess of my sequel
查询位我续集的资源管理器中的女主人
to manifest and use a different quiz you
表现和使用不同的测验
can do a lot of interesting things there
在那里可以做很多有趣的事情
just to keep your people away from the
只是为了让您的人民远离
code and make it as traditional and
编码并使其成为传统
dynamic as possible without having to
尽可能动态，而不必
resort to clergy area strings and lists
诉诸神职人员区域字符串和列表
and of fines all over you Java code one
并处以Java代码之一的罚款
thing we didn't get to look at in the
我们没有去看的东西
spring tip is the natural next steps now
Spring 的秘诀是自然而然的下一步
that we've got basic data access
我们已经有了基本的数据访问权限
functionality of working with my babies
与婴儿一起工作的功能
suppose we wanted to load a object graph
假设我们要加载一个对象图
which features a one-to-many
具有一对多的功能
relationship with a master object and
与主对象的关系，以及
then multiple sort of you know dependent
然后你知道多种依赖
objects you can do this very easily by
对象，您可以很容易地做到这一点
basis right it's a function of my
基本权利是我的功能
business to support loading a master
业务支持加载高手
record and providing the query to low
记录并提供低查询
the independent object in the other side
另一侧的独立对象
of the relationship and you can specify
关系的关系，您可以指定
that both in the end patients or as part
无论是最终患者还是一部分
of the XML we did all we also didn't get
在XML中，我们做了所有我们还没有得到的
to look at the right place to put this
看合适的地方放这个
data access technology in a complex
复杂的数据访问技术
application any kind of tedious data
应用任何繁琐的数据
access functionality should be in a
访问功能应位于
repository object and of course in the
存储库对象，当然在
spring framework that models itself very
本身非常建模的Spring Framework
naturally as a repository component if
自然地作为存储库组件，如果
you have functionality that is meant to
您的功能旨在
be atomic maybe you want to do multiple
是原子的，也许你想做多个
things in kind of a single atomic body
单个原子体中的事物
of work or batch of work you can
您可以进行的一项或多项工作
decorate your methods with a
用一个装饰你的方法
transactional render Springs very much a
事务性渲染Springs非常
transactional but you can see the spring
事务性的，但您可以看到 Spring
tip on on JTA for a little bit more on
在JTA上获得更多提示
this and there's numerous other
这个还有很多其他的
resources on that as well so consider
资源，所以也考虑
that while we've been a just a cursory
那虽然我们只是一个粗略的
look at what you which can be done with
看看你可以做什么
my babies this kind of functionality the
我的宝宝这种功能
data access functionality should live
数据访问功能应该生效
and replies repository object alright
并回复存储库对象
with that all thanks for watching and
感谢您的收看和
we'll see you on next
我们下次见